

MATERIALS ENGINEER

# Personal Information



(+57) 301-433-73-18



Medellin-Colombia



danilomorales110@gmail.com darmito10@gmail.com



LinkedIn: @danilomorales110



github: darmo1

Languages
English:intermediate



Hobbies
I like training in gym
I love soccer sport and
Coffe

# DANILO ARTURO MORALES PULGARIN

Danilo is a materials engineer with a great passion for computer science, he likes frontend technologies and he has worked with React Js, Next Js, JavaScript, Firebase, and he has worked with content management systems (CMS) such as Sanity, and WordPress. He likes to keep updating on front-end technologies and enjoys teamwork, learning new skills, and solving problems. Danilo wishes to merge the materials science and IT areas.

Core competencies: web technologies

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### COMONO COLOMBIA WEBSITE

2021.06 - 2021.08 WWW.COMONOCOLOMBIA.COM TECHNOLOGIES: NEXT.JS, SANITY, HTML, CSS

## CLOSER - MVP - FIRST VERSION

2021.02 - 2021.05 CLOSER-353AB.FIREBASEAPP.COM TECHNOLOGIES: NEXT.JS, FIREBASE, HTML, CSS

#### SUPPORT VAAR WEBSITE

2020.05 - 2020.12 WWW.VAAR.LAW
TECHNOLOGIES: WORDPRESS, REACT, PHP, HTML, CSS

#### SUPPORT STARTUP CFO WEBSITE

2020.06 - 2020.12 STARTUPCFO.COMONOPRESS.COM TECHNOLOGIES: WORDPRESS, PHP, HTML, CSS

## EDUCATION

# **REACT JS**

PLATZI - 2021

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PLATZI - DECEMBER 2019

# JAVASCRIPT FUNDAMENTALS

PLATZI - NOVEMBER 2019

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT BASIC

FRONTEND

PLATZI - NOVEMBER. 2019

# FUNDAMENTALS OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

PLATZI -SEPTEMBER 2019

## INTRODUCTION STRUCTURED PROGRAMMING

PLATZI -SEPTEMBER2019

## DEGREE

BACHELOR MATERIALS ENGINEER
ANTIOQUIA UNIVERSITY AUGUST 2011 - AUGUSTO 2018